But Kazami Hayato is approaching from their rear!
It's a 4 second difference to the top!
He's slipstreaming Bootsvorz...
Is it Kazami?!
Let's go!
He overtook him!
Now he's in 3rd!
Hayato...
Luck was on your side today.
But do not think it was because of your abilities.
Everybody's eyes are on this final lap!
Can Kazami Hayato make a miraculous comeback?!
Feel like a fire each time I go
Chief!
Feel like a ray of sunlight
Hey!
I'm sorry, Chief-san.
Go down the road on wheels of gold
I've been so selfish.
I've got a dream at midnight
Sugo's chief is you.
Come with me, catch a flash of light
I'm counting on you.
Sure!
Into the heavens
How are your hands?
Come with me, roll the dice of right
They're fine.
They're naturally strong.
Seven come eleven
Don't force yourself.
Asurada's coming.
Reach out
Yes!
take it now like there's no today
I've got to ride
Asurada, I'm going to win today's race no matter what!
Fly high
I'll fight it out on the last corner. Let's go!
'Cause you know that it's the only way
Impossible... it'll go over the limit.
Today... I have no limit!
I've got to ride
Ride hard
ride it now and sail into the wind
Samurai Boy.
He's here.
Run like a child
Effect fan activate!
Roger.
Flat out
What?!
go for broke and you can really win it
Go!
Go hide and wild
Kazami Hayato and Super Asurada Double-One,
they overcame their obstacles
and made a majestic, triumphant return!